Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ laurenaubreylee (LinkedIn) www.laurenaubreylee.com/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

User Interface Design User Experience (UX) Graphic Design

Certifications
UX/UI Design Flex Program

Honors-Awards

Create-a-Thon
Disney Imagineering Competition
Dean's Scholar Award
Japan Center Garages Logo Contest

Lauren Aubrey Lee

UI/UX Designer | Graphic Designer | Illustrator | Community Builder San Francisco, California, United States

Summary

I am a UX/UI Designer with 5+ years of Graphic Design and Illustration experience. I aspire to create genuinely effective UI designs by improving my designs according to users' voiced frustrations. My strengths in empathizing with both users and engineers make me a strong team member that will not only ensure the right design is created for the user, but also that the process of building it goes as smoothly as possible.

Technical Skills: UX Research, UI Design, Graphic Design, Wireframing, Information Architecture, Prototyping, Interaction Design, Branding, Visual Design, Illustration Software: Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Procreate, Microsoft Office

Portfolio: https://www.laurenaubreylee.com/

Experience

Chop Dawg UI/UX Designer November 2022 - Present (1 year)

- Collaborate with product managers, developers, and other stakeholders to create user-centered designs for web and mobile applications.
- Create wireframes, user flows, prototypes, and high-fidelity mockups using Figma.
- Continuously iterate and improve designs based on user feedback, data analysis, and industry trends.

Meetup Event Organizer July 2022 - Present (1 year 4 months) San Francisco Bay Area Event Organizer for Boba Buddies SF: https://www.meetup.com/bobabuddiessf/

- Create, facilitate and market Boba Buddies activities to promote social and interpersonal relationships among members through Meetup.
- Organize, plan, and coordinate events with 30+ members on a weekly basis.
- Manage and maintain a Discord server to facilitate communication and engagement among members, including moderating discussions, troubleshooting technical issues, and enforcing community guidelines.
- Mediate and find solutions for all parties involved when disagreements happen between members.

Albert's List

Community Manager, San Francisco September 2022 - September 2023 (1 year 1 month)

San Francisco, California, United States

- Curate bi-monthly events that bring in up to 150+ guests.
- Successfully plan, organize, and execute engaging online and offline community events to foster a sense of community among members.
- Execute and promote events through various social media platforms, including Facebook, LinkedIn, and Eventbrite, to increase event attendance and engagement.

CASSANDRA BANKSON LLC

Lead Graphic Designer October 2020 - July 2021 (10 months)

- Created designs used in merchandise and illustrations used in various social media platforms.
- Designs and illustrations were created using Procreate, Adobe Illustrator, and Adobe Photoshop.

AEW ENGINEERING, INC.

Administrative Assistant September 2019 - May 2021 (1 year 9 months) San Francisco Bay Area

- Helped with payroll and AR/AP through Quickbooks
- Communicated with staff to create meetings and assist them as needed

Socialhaus

Community Lead & Social Media Strategist March 2019 - March 2020 (1 year 1 month)

San Francisco Bay Area

- Managed and created social media posts while also designing advertisements for Facebook, Instagram, and Linkedin.
- Identified and analyzed relevant key performance indicators to measure the success of community engagement strategies.
- Helped facilitate bi-weekly events for groups of 50+ people.

Paper Culture

Seasonal Production Artist & Customer Advocate November 2018 - December 2018 (2 months)

- Guided customers throughout their design process
- Edited photos and type on cards making sure they came out perfect
- Messaged and called customers through Zendesk

Petzila Inc.

Graphic Design and Advertising Intern September 2016 - July 2017 (11 months) San Jose, California

- · Collaborated in a team of four interns
- Created brand material for the company that included landing pages, business cards, and print/web based advertisements.
- Worked with company leadership to create marketing plans for current and new products.
- Managed social media content such as Instagram, Facebook, and their personal app

Talbots

Sales Associate

February 2016 - May 2017 (1 year 4 months)

San Jose, California

- · Assisted customers throughout the store
- · Performed cashier duties
- Had personal shopper duties that included calling customers about new products and promotions
- · Kept the store clean and organized

Cary Lane

Visual Design Intern June 2013 - August 2013 (3 months)

• Created signs and promotional advertisements for the store

Education

San Jose State University

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Design Studies with an emphasis in Graphic Design, Minor in Advertising · (2013 - 2018)

Thinkful

UX/UI Design Flex Program · (August 2021 - February 2022)

City College of San Francisco

· (2013 - 2013)